{"id":"2017_3","name":"Romans2017_3","memoryVerse":"“For since the creation of the world, God’s invisible qualities – his eternal power and divine nature – have been clearly seen, being understood from what has been made, so that people are without excuse.” – Romans 1:20 ","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2017_3_1","questionText":"1. What was meaningful to you in the lecture?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_3_2","questionText":"2. What help did you receive from the notes?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read Romans 2:1-4.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"2:1-4"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_3_3","questionText":"3. Why are the people in this passage without excuse, and upon what does God base His judgment?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_3_4","questionText":"4. What does it mean to pass judgment, and how does this differ from knowing and teaching God’s standards? Tell how you struggle with passing judgment on others.","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_3_5","questionText":"5. How has God showered you with kindness and patience, and how do you demonstrate these godly attributes toward others?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read Romans 2:5-16.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"2:5-16"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_3_6","questionText":"6. What do stubborn, unrepentant people store up for themselves, and what are you storing up? (See also Matthew 6:19-20; 12:35.)  ","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Matthew","verse":"6:19-20"},{"book":"Matthew","verse":"12:35"}]},{"id":"2017_3_7a","questionText":"7. a. From verses 7-11, list the results when people follow the path of good and when they follow the path of evil.","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_3_7b","questionText":"7. b. What do your actions reveal about your heart attitude toward God?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_3_8","questionText":"8. What standard will God use to judge people’s obedience?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read Romans 2:17-24.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"2:17-24"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_3_9a","questionText":"9. a. What privileges did God give the Jews, and what was their attitude toward their privileges?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_3_9b","questionText":"9. b.  What specific privileges has He given you, and how do you sometimes demonstrate the same attitude?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_3_10","questionText":"10. Which of the 10 Commandments did Paul accuse the Jews of breaking? List some common ways Christians who teach others about following Jesus fail to do what He says? (See Exodus 20:1-17; Matthew 7:21-23.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Exodus","verse":"20:1-17"},{"book":"Matthew","verse":"7:21-23"}]},{"id":"2017_3_11","questionText":"11. What happens when any religious person violates the standards they proclaim? Is there an area of your life in which you may be guilty of this?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read Romans 2:25-29.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"2:25-29"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_3_12a","questionText":"12. a. What is circumcision, and why would this sign be a source of pride? (See Genesis 17:1-14.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Genesis","verse":"17:1-14"}]},{"id":"2017_3_12b","questionText":"12. b. Name some outward signs people today rely on to be in right relationship with God.","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_3_13","questionText":"13. According to this passage, what is a true Jew, and what does this mean to you?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review Romans 2.","questions":[{"id":"2017_3_14","questionText":"14. What have you learned about God in this week’s study? How may your group pray for you as you make this truth a part of your life?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]}}}